welcome back to your tuned in to boss
out Morning Call here on CNBC TV TV it's
a special day because it's our 23
23rd but we need to track some stocks
for you and our entire research team is
joining in
stop though let's uh you know address
one of the top stocks that will be in
Focus hdfcmc nimesh joins us uh welcome
I'm going to be practically the most
informed person today because nimesh and
we are going to be on the road but tell
us you're tracking hcfc MC a lot
straight is already watching out for uh
yes Nigel it's in a big surprise move
last evening uh you know Aberdeen Asset
Management who's the co-sponsor of HDFC
AMC has gone ahead and said that they
want to sell their entire 10.2 percent
stake in HDFC AMC they will cease to be
the co-sponsor of hdmc hdfcmc going
forward but interestingly out of that
10.2 percent they're willing to sell 9.9
stake to just a single buyer that's
going to be very important because you
know that will remove the overall uh you
know supply overrank of agility remember
that hdfcmc has been a rank under
performer in the last one year and there
has been this concern about everything
selling stakes and now they've gone
ahead and said they want to sell to a
single buyer that will be very important
in fact Jeffries put out a note today
morning and they said they will require
the unit holder approval as well if
there is no exemptions that is something
to watch out for but what I understand
from source is that one single buyer is
likely to be a large private Equity
player so very important deal and hdf
same civil will be in the green I
believe because the concern of a big or
flower rank will be out of the way all
right so while they're selling I think
that last point is important note thanks
for that overhang with this stake sale
perhaps out of the way once this is done
that is now Siemens is the next one in
Focus uh they've emerged as the lowest
bidder for a large project vaishta is
here with details to hi hi prashan good
morning for Siemens as you rightly
mentioned it has emerged as the lowest
bidder for the 9000 horsepower electric
locomotives project in the whole which
is in Gujarat mcquery says that the
order would be substantially higher than
the current order backlog as on 30th of
September 2022 the order backlog was at
70 100 crores macquery expects a robust
order in flow for the mobility segment
to continue an fy23 and factors in a 23
percent keger order inflow for the
mobility segment over fy21 to fy25 my
query has an outperformed rating on the
stock with a Target price of 3120 rupees
okay that's a big upside to the current
market price 3120 is the Target that
Macquarie has thanks a lot for that
let's go across to surbi now she's
tracking some of the insurance companies
this morning survey what's the news
there
hi thanks for that The General Insurance
data for the month of November was out
last evening and the industry saw a
strong premium growth for ICICI and
Lombard the November premium was up 19
on a year-on-year basis and year to date
it grew by 22 on market share front also
it gained 40 basis points this month
Standalone health insurance also saw a
strong growth of 34 of which star health
insurance grew by 16 on a year-on-year
basis and year to date it grew by 12
percent the market was marginally down
close to 18 basis points for the month
but overall good numbers from General
insurance companies stocks will react
today thanks very much surprised for
that because the recent uh recently
listed the snacks player reported
numbers for the second quarter sonal is
here with details good morning Prashant
with a good set of numbers by bikaji in
the second quarter Revenue growth of
31.5 on a yui basis leading to any
better growth of 40 there was a margin
expansion as well to the tune of a
hundred basis points coming in at 11.4
percent leading to a profit growth of 43
now remember the stock listed at a
premium and since its listing also it's
up 25 and at these levels it trades
around 77 times one year forward
earnings so not cheap at all and looks
like these results have been priced in
as well but the price action today is
something we'll be watching out for
going with green on bikaji today okay
bikaji in fact that stock I mean it's
what about almost 30 percent since
listing and as the sonal was telling us
very expensive now almost 78 times so I
guess um that pricing and a lot of the
good news but let's go across to Vivek
he's talking about Craftsman auto and
Sapphire
what's the latest there
well good morning you know it's actually
been a clean out trade as far as
Craftsman auto is concerned so you know
fund by the name of Marina Singapore PT
limited actually sold its entire 11.56
per 11.56 flag shares in the company
which had you know came to around five
and a half percent stake in the company
now very interestingly the buyers have
been marking names so why to Capital
Management picked up almost 1.28
lectures Abu Dhabi investment Authority
picked up 2.4 lakh shares and India
Acorn what almost 3.33 lakhs so expect
some green on this particular stock in
today's trading session on the other
hand Sapphire food you know we are going
with the red in this particular name
what's actually happened over there is
the fact that fennel private limited
that held almost a significant stake of
2.77 and the company has spared a bit of
its take has sold
6.01 lectures in the company and you
know given the fact that there exists an
overhang or further stake sale we are
going with the red on this particular
name all right Vivek thank you very much
for that so lots of deals lots of blocks
happening have been happening for the
last many months now and these are the
latest now more stocks with new slow
service here with the lists would be
high
so for five PESA the board has approved
the merger with iifl Securities online
retail trading business the online
business revenue for the month for fi22
was approximately 52 crores now this
scheme is subject to many regulatory
approvals but if it goes through for
every one share of five PESA Capital you
will receive 50 shares of IFL Securities
next is elcon where the company has
received an end-to-end order that is
from procurement to certifying from Sri
Lanka Railways the order is worth 122
crores and the contract figure is nearly
24 months okay thanks a lot for that
survey well the other big headline is
what's happened